Register of the George Sokolsky Papers, 1916-1962
Hoover Institution Archives
- CORRESPONDENCE, 1916-1962
  - Los Angeles Herald and Express, 1946-1953 (Folder 10)
  - The Lotos Club, 1953-1960 (Folder 11)
  - Lovell, Malcom, 1941-1960 (Folder 12)
  - Lovering, Frank W., 1948-1949 (Folder 13)
  - Lovestone, Jay, 1946-1962 (Folder 14)
  - Lowe, Pardee, 1934 (Folder 15)
  - Lowenthal, Marvin, 1945 (Folder 16)
  - Luce, Clare Booth, 1933-1959 (Folder 17)
  - Luce, Henry, 1933-1944 (Folder 18)
  - Lucullus Circle, 1951-1962. (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Luhnow, Christian C., 1954 (Folder 2)
  - Lund, Robert, 1938-1951 (Folder 3)
  - Lundberg, Ferdinand, 1939 (Folder 4)
  - Lurie, Louis, 1955-1956 (Folder 5)
  - Lutz, Ralph H., 1948-1951 (Folder 6)
  - Lynch, John, 1945 (Folder 7)
  - Lyons, Eugene, 1939-1962 (Folder 8)
  - Lyons, Leonard, 1951-1952 (Folder 9)
  - Lytton, Henry D., 1960-1962 (Folder 10)
  - MacAlarney, Robert E., 1941-1942 (Folder 11)
  - MacArthur, Douglas, 1956-1960 (Folder 12)
  - MacBain, Merle, 1949-1950 (Folder 13)
  - McCabe, Charles, 1946-1962 (Folder 14)
  - McCarey, Leo, 1950-1959 (Folder 15)
  - McCarran, Margaret, 1953 (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - McCarran, Pat, Mr. and Mrs., 1951-1954 (Folder 2)
  - McCarthy, Joseph R., Mr. and Mrs., 1950-1959 (Folder 3)
  - McCarthy Club, 1952 (Folder 4)
  - McCauley, Raymond, 1952-1960 (Folder 5)
  - McColloch, Claude, 1953-1956 (Folder 6)
  - McCormick, Chauncey, 1942-1953 (Folder 7)
  - McCormick, Robert L. L., 1959-1961 (Folder 8)
  - McCormick, Robert R., 1942-1952 (Folder 9)
  - McDonald, James G., 1939-1944 (Folder 10)
  - McGrath, W. L., 1955 (Folder 11)
  - McCullough, John T., Mrs.
    - 1949
      - August-October (Folder 12)
      - November-December (Folder 13)
    - 1950 (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - McGranery, James P., 1952-1958 (Folder 2)
  - McGraw-Hill Book Co., 1952-1953 (Folder 3)
  - McGuinness, James, Mr. and Mrs., 1950-1957 (Folder 4)
  - McGuire, John, 1958-1959 (Folder 5)
  - McGurrin, James, 1952-1961 (Folder 6)
  - McIntyre, Francis Cardinal, 1948-1960 (Folder 7)
  - McLaughlin, Tom, 1956-1958 (Folder 8)
  - MacLean, James N., 1942-1949 (Folder 9)
  - McLearn, Frank C., 1961-1962 (Folder 10)
  - McMahon, Brien, 1949-1950 (Folder 11)
  - McMahon, Thomas, 1946-1947 (Folder 12)
  - McManus, Terence, 1943-1948 (Folder 13)
  - McMullen, Declan X., 1946-1950 (Folder 14)
  - MacMurray, John V., 1925-1936 (Folder 15)
  - MacNair, H. F., 1924-1937 (Folder 16)
  - MacNeil, Neil, 1952-1958 (Folder 17)
  - Macy, W. Kingsland, 1945-1952 (Folder 18)
  - Madigan, John, 1951 (Folder 19)
  - Magruder, John, 1920-1939 (Folder 20)
  - Maines, George H., 1942-1961 (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Maisel, Robert, 1943-1945 (Folder 2)
  - Malmed, A. T., 1944 (Folder 3)
  - Malone, George, Mr. and Mrs., 1950-1958 (Folder 4)
  - Malone, John, 1958-1959 (Folder 5)
  - Mandel, Benjamin
    - 1937-1951 (Folder 6)
    - 1952-1962 (Folder 7)
  - Manheim, Kate C., 1957-1958 (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - Marache, Herbert, 1962 (Folder 2)
  - Marco Polo Club, 1959-1960 (Folder 3)
  - Marinette Eagle-Star, 1944-1947 (Folder 4)
  - Markel, Lester, 1931-1950 (Folder 5)
  - Marsden, Carl, 1938 (Folder 6)
  - Marsh, Edward G., 1954-1956 (Folder 7)
  - Marshall, James, 1916-1953 (Folder 8)
  - Marshall, John, 1958-1959 (Folder 9)
  - Marshall, Verne, 1940 (Folder 10)
  - Martin, I. Jack, Mr. and Mrs., 1953-1956 (Folder 11)
  - Martin, Joseph W., Jr., 1944-1955 (Folder 12)
  - Marx, Robert S., 1958-1959 (Folder 13)
  - Marymount College, 1961-1962 (Folder 14)
  - Masliansky, H., 1918-1953 (Folder 15)
  - Mason, Frank E., 1946-1960 (Folder 16)
  - Mathews, William R., 1942-1949 (Folder 17)
  - Matsuoka, Yosuke, 1928-1935 (Folder 18)
  - Mattei, Albert C., Mr. and Mrs., 1940-1960 (Folder 19)
  - Matthews, J. B., Mr. and Mrs. (Box 87)
    - 1937-1940 (Folder 1)
    - 1941-1949 (Folder 2)
    - 1950-1961 (Folder 3)
  - Matthews, Ruth S., 1958-1961 (Folder 4)
  - Maxwell, Elsa, 1942-1944 (Folder 5)
  - May, Armand, 1939-1943 (Folder 6)
  - Mayer, Ferdinand L., 1953-1962 (Folder 7)
  - Mayer, Louis B., 1956 (Folder 8)
  - Mead, Joseph, 1938-1948 (Folder 9)
  - Meehan, James, 1950 (Folder 10)
  - Meharg, Lawrence, Mr. and Mrs., 1934-1962 (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - Meigs, Merrill, 1953-1961 (Folder 2)
  - Menjou, Adolphe, 1947-1962 (Folder 3)
  - Mennell, Peter, 1955-1956 (Folder 4)
  - Merritt, Max, 1949-1961 (Folder 5)
  - Merson, Martin, 1953-1956 (Folder 6)
  - Metzner, Katherine M., 1945-1959 (Folder 7)
  - Meyner, Robert B., Mrs., 1960 (Folder 8)
  - Mickelson, Walter K., 1944-1948 (Folder 9)
  - Miles, Richard, 1959-1960 (Folder 10)
  - Millard, Thomas F., 1921-1924 (Folder 11)
  - Miller, Bernice, 1961 (Folder 12)
  - Miller, Clyde, 1937-1941 (Folder 13)
  - Miller, Dickenson S., 1917-1935 (Folder 14)
  - Miller, Hugh Gordon, 1962 (Folder 15)
  - Mills, Ogden, Mr. and Mrs., 1934-1950 (Folder 16)
  - Milwaukee Sentinel, 1947-1956 (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - Mintzer, George J., 1946-1949 (Folder 2)
  - Misselwitz, Henry, 1938-1939 (Folder 3)
  - Miyakawa, T. Scott, 1939-1953 (Folder 4)
  - Moley, Raymond, 1939-1956 (Folder 5)
  - Montana School of Mines, 1948-1961 (Folder 6)
  - Montgomery, George S., Jr., 1940-1954 (Folder 7)
  - Moore, Frederick, 1919-1951 (Folder 8)
  - Morawets, Marjorie, 1949-1953 (Folder 9)
  - Morgenthau, Henry, 1926-1933 (Folder 10)
  - Morris, Newbold, 1944-1945 (Folder 11)
  - Morris, Robert, 1951-1962 (Folder 12)
  - Morris, William, 1926-1933 (Folder 13)
  - Moser, C. K., 1931-1936 (Folder 14)
  - Moses, Robert, 1942-1962 (Folder 15)
  - Moskovics, F. E., 1959 (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - Moskovit, Harold R., 1954-1956 (Folder 2)
  - Motley, Arthur H., 1960 (Folder 3)
  - Moyle, Donald, 1961 (Folder 4)
  - Mullen, Frank E., 1943-1956 (Folder 5)
  - Mulvey, James, 1952-1954 (Folder 6)
  - Mundt, Karl, Mr. and Mrs., 1941-1960 (Folder 7)
  - Murphy, George, 1954-1962 (Folder 8)
  - Murray, Thomas E., 1953-1959 (Folder 9)
  - Musmanno, Michael A., 1953-1960 (Folder 10)
  - Nashville Banner, 1946-1955. Includes correspondence with James G. Stahlman (Folder 11)
  - The Nation, 1941 (Folder 12)
  - National Association of Manufacturers, 1937-1957. Includes correspondence with Elizabeth S. Cowles, Eldorous Dayton, John C. Gall, John C. Gebhart, Clifford Harrison, Charles R. Hook, William Lawson (Folder 13)
  - Morris M. Lee, Noel Sargent, Walter B. Weisenburger
  - and Clarence M. Wright
  - National Committee on Food for the Small Democracies, 1941-1944 (Folder 14)
  - National Council to Combat Blindness, 1946-1955 (Folder 15)
  - National Republican Club, 1937-1941 (Folder 16)
  - National Review, 1958-1961 (Folder 17)
  - National Steel Corporation, 1938-1946 (Folder 18)
  - Neel, Bill, 1960 (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - Neuser, Francis, 1953 (Folder 2)
  - New Britain Herald, 1948-1956 (Folder 3)
  - The New Haven Register, 1947-1953 (Folder 4)
  - New Orleans States, 1951-1953 (Folder 5)
  - The New York Evening Post, 1927 (Folder 6)
  - New York Heart Association, 1957-1960 (Folder 7)
  - New York Herald Tribune, 1936-1956 (Folder 8)
  - New York Journal American, 1950-1962 (Folder 9)
  - New York Mirror, 1946-1962. Includes correspondence with Charles McCabe and Glen T. Neville (Folder 10)
  - New York Telephone Co., 1934 (Folder 11)
  - The New York Times, 1933-1962 (Folder 12)
  - Newhouse, Samuel I., Jr., 1945-1962 (Folder 13)
  - The News and Courier, 1942-1960 (Folder 14)
  - The News-Gazette, 1945-1953 (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - News Publishing Co., 1944-1956 (Folder 2)
  - The News-Sentinel, 1944-1951 (Folder 3)
  - Nichols, Hayden, Mr. and Mrs., 1923-1960 (Folder 4)
  - Nichols, Louis B., 1958-1962 (Folder 5)
  - Nichols, William, 1949-1962 (Folder 6)
  - Nimitz, Chester, 1951 (Folder 7)
  - Nixon, Richard M., 1950-1962 (Folder 8)
  - Noble, Edward J., 1944-1958 (Folder 9)
  - North, Raymond E., 1946 (Folder 10)
  - North-China Daily News, 1922-1930 (Folder 11)
  - The Norwalk Hour, 1951-1953 (Folder 12)
  - Nover, Barnet, 1929-191938 (Folder 13)
  - Nuttall, Ruth, 1959 (Folder 14)
  - O'Brien, Frank, 1938-1942 (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - O'Connor, Kathryn, 1951 (Folder 2)
  - Odagiri, Masunosuke, 1925-1928 (Folder 3)
  - Odets, Clifford, 1952 (Folder 4)
  - O'Hara, John Cardinal, 1958 (Folder 5)
  - O'Neil, James, 1951-1960 (Folder 6)
  - Ormerod, Berkeley, Sir, 1948-1962 (Folder 7)
  - Our Sunday Visitor, 1945-1951 (Folder 8)
  - Oursler, Fulton, Mr. and Mrs., 1940-1955 (Folder 9)
  - Overseas Press Club of America, 1939-1961 (Folder 10)
  - Padway, Joseph A., 1938-1939 (Box 94, Folder 1)
  - The Palladium Publishing Co., 1948-1959 (Folder 2)
  - Paramore, Edward, 1933-1935 (Folder 3)
  - Parks, F. L., 1947-1948 (Folder 4)
  - Patriotic Education, Inc., 1953-1958 (Folder 5)
  - Patterson, Richard C., Jr., Mr. and Mrs.
    - 1921-1954 (Folder 6)
    - 1955-1962 (Folder 7)
  - Patton, Charles, 1926-1928 (Folder 8)
  - Patton, George, Mrs., 1946-1950 (Folder 9)
  - Payne, Frederick G., 1957 (Folder 10)
  - Payne, Harry, 1934-1940 (Folder 11)
  - Peacock, Roscoe
    - 1936-1940 (Folder 12)
    - 1941-1943 (Box 95, Folder 1)
    - 1944-1951 (Folder 2)
  - Peale, Norman Vincent, Mr. and Mrs., 1940-1958 (Folder 3)
  - Peck, David W., 1952 (Folder 4)
  - Pegler, Westbrook, 1945-1961 (Folder 5)
  - Pei, Mario, 1944-1953 (Folder 6)
  - The Peoria Journal Star, 1944-1959 (Folder 7)
  - Perlman, Phyllis, 1919-1923 (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - Persons, Wilton, 1949-1956 (Folder 2)
  - Petrov, Vladimir, 1960-1961 (Folder 3)
  - Phang, Inez, 1920-1927 (Folder 4)
  - The Philadelphia Inquirer, 1943-1951. Includes correspondence with Walter Annenberg, John Trevor Curtis, and E. B. Thompson (Folder 5)
  - Philoon, Wallace, 1921 (Folder 6)
  - Pitcher, Conrad N., 1939-1943 (Folder 7)
  - Pitkin, Walter, 1917-1937 (Folder 8)
  - Plavner, Murray, 1938-1945 (Folder 9)
  - Police Athletic League, 1957-1958 (Folder 10)
  - Pollock, Channing, 1936-1946 (Folder 11)
  - Porter, Seton, 1949-1950 (Folder 12)
  - The Post-Standard, 1945-1954 (Folder 13)
  - Pott, F. L. Hawks, 1925-1933 (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - Potter, T. Irving, 1948 (Folder 2)
  - Powell, J. B.
    - 1918-1927 (Folder 3)
    - 1928-1933 (Folder 4)
  - Powell, John W., 1947 (Folder 5)
  - Pratt, Ruth, 1937-1940 (Folder 6)
  - Prentis, H. W., Jr., 1940-1948 (Folder 7)
  - Pressman, Lee, 1941 (Folder 8)
  - Pryor, Samuel F., 1945-1957 (Folder 9)
  - Public Ledger, 1925-1927 (Folder 10)
  - Queeny, Edgar Monsanto, 1943-1953 (Folder 11)
  - Quezon, Manuel L., 1925-1935 (Folder 12)
  - Quo, Tai-chi, 1921-1941 (Folder 13)
  - Radziwill, Catherine, 1939 (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Rager, Edward, 1939-1946 (Folder 2)
  - Rajchman, Ludwik, 1930-1931 (Folder 3)
  - The Raleigh Times, 1952 (Folder 4)
  - Rea, George Bronson
  - Rand, Ayn, 1941-1946 (Folder 5)
    - 1925-1927 (Folder 6)
    - 1928 (Folder 7)
    - 1929 (Folder 8)
    - 1930-1936 (Folder 9)
  - Rea, Gloria, 1942-1951 (Box 99, Folder 1)
  - Rea, Henry Carter, 1951-1956 (Folder 2)
  - Read, Leonard E., 1944-1951 (Folder 3)
  - Reardon, Mary, 1945-1948 (Folder 4)
  - Regnery, Henry, 1951-1961 (Folder 5)
  - Reid, Helen Rogers, 1934-1950 (Folder 6)
  - Renaud, Ralph, 1927-1934 (Folder 7)
  - Republican National Committee, 1938-1951 (Folder 8)
  - ReQua, Eloise, 1932-1941 (Folder 9)
  - Rhea, Fred K., 1962 (Folder 10)
  - Rhodes, Irwin S., 1955-1960 (Folder 11)
  - Ribicoff, Abraham, 1954-1955 (Folder 12)
  - Richardson, H. Smith, 1939-1940 (Folder 13)
  - The Richmond News-Leader, 1949-1956 (Folder 14)
  - Rickard, Edgar, 1937-1951 (Folder 15)
  - Rickenbacker, Edward, 1953-1961 (Folder 16)
  - Rickover, Hyman G., 1958-1962 (Folder 17)
  - Ridder, Victor, 1943-1962 (Box 100, Folder 1)
  - Ries, Maurice, 1954-1959 (Folder 2)
  - Rimanoczy, Richard S., 1946-1959 (Folder 3)
  - Ritchie, John
    - 1938-1944 (Folder 4)
    - 1945-1946 (Folder 5)
    - 1947-1948 (Folder 6)
  - Roberts, George, Jr., 1938-1947 (Folder 7)
  - Robinson, Edward G., 1952-1953 (Folder 8)
  - Robnett, George, 1944-1951 (Folder 9)
  - Rock, Lewis B., Jr., 1960 (Folder 10)
  - Rockefeller, John D., Jr., 1944-1949 (Folder 11)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson, 1949 (Folder 12)
  - Rogers, Coré, 1945 (Folder 13)
  - Rooney, John J., 1955 (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - Roosevelt, Archibald B., Mr. and Mrs., 1953-1961 (Folder 2)
  - Roosevelt, Kermit, 1931-1936 (Folder 3)
  - Roosevelt, Theodore, 1934-1941 (Folder 4)
  - Roots, John, 1937-1961 (Folder 5)
  - Roots, Logan H., 1935-1945 (Folder 6)
  - Rose, Archibald, 1927-1933 (Folder 7)
  - Rosenblatt, William, 1931-1938 (Folder 8)
  - Rosenblum, William F., 1944 (Folder 9)
  - Rosenman, Samuel, 1959-1960 (Folder 10)
  - Rosensteil, Lewis S., 1948-1960 (Folder 11)
  - Ross, T. J., 1937-1956 (Folder 12)
  - The Rotarian, 1944-1946 (Folder 13)
  - Rothman, A. D., 1920-1946 (Folder 14)
  - Rotonda, Armand, 1961 (Folder 15)
  - Rugg, Harold, 1941 (Folder 16)
  - Rukeyser, Merryle S., 1921-1951 (Box 102, Folder 1)
  - Rushmore, Howard, 1952-1954 (Folder 2)
  - Ryskind, Morrie, 1947-1958 (Folder 3)
  - Sachs, Alexander, 1934 (Folder 4)
  - St. Louis Globe-Democrat, 1942-1958. Includes correspondence with Richard Amberg and Lon M. Burrowes (Folder 5)
  - St. Paul Dispatch, 1944-1949 (Folder 6)
  - Samonisky, Harris, 1943-1944 (Folder 7)
  - San Francisco Call-Bulletin, 1951-1957 (Folder 8)
  - Sanger, Elliott, 1919-1927 (Folder 9)
  - Saucier, Ted, 1952-1958 (Folder 10)
  - Savannah Evening Press, 1948-1953 (Folder 11)
  - Sayre, H. D., 1941-1950 (Folder 12)
  - Scandrett, Richard B., Jr., 1941-1942 (Folder 13)
  - Scanlan, Patrick F., 1945-1958 (Folder 14)
  - Schine, G. David, 1953-1962 (Folder 15)
  - Schlink, F. J., Mr. and Mrs.
    - 1939-1941 (Folder 16)
    - 1944-1953 (Box 103, Folder 1)
  - Schultz, Benjamin, 1955-1960 (Folder 2)
  - Schurman, Jacob Gould, 1921-1932 (Folder 3)
  - Schuster, Max, 1929-1956 (Folder 4)
  - Schuyler, George, Mr. and Mrs., 1948-1959 (Folder 5)
  - Schwamm, Harvey L., 1942-1957 (Folder 6)
  - Schwamm, Jay, 1946-1954 (Folder 7)
  - Schwartz, Irving P., 1959-1960 (Folder 8)
  - Scott, Charles Ernest, 1951 (Folder 9)
  - The Scranton Times, 1943-1958 (Folder 10)
  - Scully, Frank, Mr. and Mrs. (Box 104)
    - 1917-1944 (Folder 1)
    - 1946-1960 (Folder 2)
  - Scully, William, 1943-1959 (Folder 3)
  - Seattle Post-Intelligencer, 1946-1956 (Folder 4)
  - Seligson, David, 1961-1962 (Folder 5)
  - Sell, Henry B., 1957-1961 (Folder 6)
  - Selvage, James
    - 1938-1941 (Folder 7)
    - 1942-1943 (Folder 8)
    - 1944-1947 (Box 105, Folder 1)
    - 1948-1950 (Folder 2)
    - 1951-1953 (Folder 3)
    - 1954-1955 (Folder 4)
    - 1956-1962 (Folder 5)
  - Serwer, Henry, 1947-1950 (Box 106, Folder 1)
  - Sevitzky, Fabien, 1953-1958 (Folder 2)
  - Shaffer, Isidor, 1941 (Folder 3)
  - Shallcross, Ruth, 1948-1949 (Folder 4)
  - Shanahan, Thomas J., 1943-1960 (Folder 5)
  - Shanghai (China). Commissioner of Police, 1927 (Folder 6)
  - Shanghai Tiffin Club, 1959 (Folder 7)
  - Shankman, Jacob K., 1945 (Folder 8)
  - Shapiro, Nathan D., 1946-1951 (Folder 9)
  - Shaw, Arch W., 1943-1951 (Folder 10)
  - Sheldon, Ruth, 1937-1940 (Folder 11)
  - Shiber, Haviv, 1959 (Folder 12)
  - Shigemitsu, Mamoru, 1930-1956 (Folder 13)
  - Shotwell, James T., 1931-1949 (Folder 14)
  - Shulman, Charles E., 1939-1941 (Folder 15)
  - Silbey, Celia, 1953 (Folder 16)
  - Silbey, Stanley, 1944-1959 (Folder 17)
  - Silver, Abba Hillel, 1934-1945 (Folder 18)
  - Silver, Charles H., 1949-1961 (Folder 19)
  - Silver, H. Richard, 1960 (Folder 20)
  - Simms, Albert G., 1945 (Folder 21)
  - Simms, Ruth H., 1944 (Folder 22)
  - Simons, George Albert, 1944-1950 (Folder 23)
  - Simpson, Malcom, 1930-1946 (Folder 24)
  - Sinclair, Upton, 1935-1940 (Folder 25)
  - Sino-American Amity, Inc., 1953-1962 (Folder 26)
  - Skouras, Spyros P., 1944-1955 (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - Sloan, Alfred P., Jr., 1943-1955 (Folder 2)
  - Smith, Alfred E., 1942-1944 (Folder 3)
  - Smith, Carleton, 1950 (Folder 4)
  - Smith, Douglas M., 1950 (Folder 5)
  - Smith, Earl, 1960-1962 (Folder 6)
  - Smith, Elizur Yale
    - 1944-1947 (Folder 7)
    - 1948-1949 (Folder 8)
  - Smith, George H. E., 1944-1945 (Folder 9)
  - Smith, Gerald L. K., 1941-1962 (Folder 10)
  - Smith, Gertrude Robinson, 1954-1957 (Folder 11)
  - Smith, H. Alexander, 1940-1951 (Box 108, Folder 1)
  - Smith, Joseph Kingsbury, 1956-1962 (Folder 2)
  - Smith, W. Bedell, 1950-1955 (Folder 3)
  - Smith, William J., 1944-1947 (Folder 4)
  - Sokolski, Samuel S., 1957-1962 (Folder 5)
  - Sokolsky, David, 1958 (Folder 6)
  - Sokolsky, Mollie, n.d. (Folder 7)
  - Sokolsky (née Phang), Rosalind, 1919 (Folder 8)
  - Sokolsky, Sulamith, 1960-1961 (Folder 9)
  - Soong, T. V.
    - 1918-1929 (Folder 10)
    - 1930
      - January-October (Folder 11)
      - November-December (Folder 12)
    - 1931-1933 (Folder 13)
  - Sourwine, J. G., 1955-1961 (Box 109, Folder 1)
  - Spangler, Fred T., 1949-1960 (Folder 2)
  - Spangler, Harrison E., 1943-1952 (Folder 3)
  - Spellman, Francis, Cardinal, 1943-1961 (Folder 4)
  - Spingold, Nate B., 1953-1958 (Folder 5)
  - Spivak, Lawrence E., 1948-1956 (Folder 6)
  - Sprague, J. Russel, 1942-1948 (Folder 7)
  - The Standard-Times, 1948-1960 (Folder 8)
  - Stansbury, H. A., 1944-1949 (Folder 9)
  - Stassen, Harold E., 1949-1957 (Folder 10)
  - Steinbrink, Meier, 1946-1956 (Folder 11)
  - Steinbrocker, Otto, 1949-1959 (Folder 12)
  - Stern, Donald, Mr. and Mrs., 1928-1955 (Folder 13)
  - Stevens, F. W., 1920-1926 (Folder 14)
  - Stevenson, Archibald, 1942-1944 (Folder 15)
  - Stessel, Paul, 1946-1949 (Folder 16)
  - Stevenson, Edward and Suzanne, 1951-1956 (Folder 17)
  - Steyne, Alan, 1932-1934 (Folder 18)
  - Stim, Menahem, 1946 (Box 110, Folder 1)
  - Stoddard, Lothrop, 1932-1933 (Folder 2)
  - Stoeckel, Herbert, 1959 (Folder 3)
  - Stolberg, Benjamin, 1941-1947 (Folder 4)
  - Stolle, Anna Lucile, 1956-1957 (Folder 5)
  - Strack, Henry De Land, Mrs., 1946 (Folder 6)
  - Strahan and Co., 1943 (Folder 7)
  - Stratton, Sally, 1953-1957 (Folder 8)
  - Straus, Lewis L., 1938-1960 (Folder 9)
  - Strawn, Silas, Mr. and Mrs., 1936-1951 (Folder 10)
  - Streit, Clarence, 1949-1961 (Folder 11)
  - Stringfellow, George E.
    - 1939-1943 (Folder 12)
    - 1944 (Folder 13)
    - 1945 (Box 111, Folder 1)
    - 1946 (Folder 2)
    - 1947-1949 (Folder 3)
    - 1950-1953 (Folder 4)
    - 1954-1959 (Folder 5)
  - Stroock, Sylvan I., 1944-1949 (Box 112, Folder 1)
  - Sullivan (née Griswold), Denny, 1950-1951 (Folder 2)
  - Sullivan, Lawrence, 1946-1948 (Folder 3)
  - Sullivan, Mark, 1937-1951 (Folder 4)
  - Sulzberger, Arthur Hays, Mr. and Mrs., 1930-1951 (Folder 5)
  - The Sun (New York). Includes correspondence with Edwin S. Friendly and Frank M. O'Brien
    - 1938-1943 (Folder 6)
    - 1944-1946 (Folder 7)
    - 1947-1950 (Folder 8)
  - Sun, Chian-fang, n.d. (Box 113, Folder 1)
  - Sun, Fo, 1926-1931 (Folder 2)
  - Sun, Yat-sen, 1919-1921 (Folder 3)
  - Sung, Hung-yi, 1920 (Folder 4)
  - Surine, 1957-1962 (Folder 5)
  - Swan, Joseph E., 1930-1960 (Folder 6)
  - Sweet, Harold R., 1942-1945 (Folder 7)
  - Swope, Herbert Bayard, 1933-1958 (Folder 8)
  - Symington, Stuart, 1951-1960 (Folder 9)
  - Taber, John, 1959 (Folder 10)
  - Taft, Hulbert, 1939-1954 (Folder 11)
  - Taft, Robert A. (Box 114)
    - 1937-1946 (Folder 1)
    - 1947-1953 (Folder 2)
  - The Tampa Daily Times, 1945-1958 (Folder 3)
  - T'ang, Shao-yi, 1919-1933 (Folder 4)
  - Tang, Yu-loo, 1925-1931 (Folder 5)
  - Taylor, Charles K., 1946-1947 (Folder 6)
  - Taylor, Henry J., 1955-1960 (Folder 7)
  - Teller, J. L., 1949 (Folder 8)
  - Texarkana Gazette, 1949-1957 (Folder 9)
  - This Week, 1936-1962. Includes correspondence with Mrs. William Brown Meloney (Folder 10)
  - Thomas, Lowell, 1937-1961 (Folder 11)
  - Thomas, Norman, 1941-1960 (Box 115, Folder 1)
  - Thompson, Clarence Smedley, 1939-1943 (Folder 2)
  - Thompson, U. T., 1958-1959 (Folder 3)
  - Thomson, Joseph, 1944-1945 (Folder 4)
  - Thurmond, Strom, 1952-1961 (Folder 5)
  - Tieje, Helen, 1943-1946 (Folder 6)
  - Tillinghast, Ray Clarke, 1944-1945 (Folder 7)
  - Timbers, William H., 1955-1960 (Folder 8)
  - Times Recorder, 1947-1949 (Folder 9)
  - The Times-Journal, 1942-1952. Includes correspondence with L. H. Dingman (Folder 10)
  - The Times-News, 1944-1945 (Folder 11)
  - The Times Union, 1945-1956. Includes correspondence with Fred Archibald (Folder 12)
  - Times-World Corp., 1947-1956 (Folder 13)
  - Ting, V. K., 1924-1932 (Folder 14)
  - Tinkham, George Holden, 1941-1952 (Folder 15)
  - Tiomkin, Dmitri, 1958-1961 (Folder 16)
  - Together, 1958 (Folder 17)
  - Tong, Edgar and Lora, 1943-1945 (Folder 18)
  - Tong, Hollington K., 1922-1958 (Box 116, Folder 1)
  - Torgut, Prince, 1918-1920 (Folder 2)
  - Tors, Ivan L., 1953 (Folder 3)
  - Touraine, George, 1956 (Folder 4)
  - Tower, Walter S., 1936-1948 (Folder 5)
  - Toynbee, Arnold, 1929-1948 (Folder 6)
  - Trammell, Niles, 1950 (Folder 7)
  - Trone, R. E., 1958-1960 (Folder 8)
  - Troster, Oliver J., 1959-1961 (Folder 9)
  - Trujillo, M. A., 1960 (Folder 10)
  - Tsur, Y. T., 1920-1927 (Folder 11)
  - Tulsa Daily World, 1943-1958 (Folder 12)
  - Tulsa Tribune, 1938 (Folder 13)
  - Turner, Paul, 1945-1946 (Folder 14)
  - Turner, William, 1959 (Folder 15)
  - Ubinger, John D., 1942-1956 (Folder 16)
  - Umstattd, William E., 1949-1953 (Folder 17)
  - Unicef, 1950-1953 (Folder 18)
  - United States. Consulate-General (Shanghai), 1920-1930 (Folder 19)
  - United States. Legation (China), 1920-1926. Includes correspondence with W. S. Drysdale, W. R. Peck, and Wallace Philoon (Folder 20)
  - United States Information Agency, 1955-1956 (Folder 21)
  - United States Post Office, 1951-1959 (Folder 22)
  - University of Notre Dame
    - 1946-1954 (Folder 23)
    - 1955-1962 (Box 117, Folder 1)
  - Utica Observer-Dispatch, 1946-1953 (Folder 2)
  - Utley, Freda, 1949 (Folder 3)
  - Van Newkirk, Charles, 1948-1949 (Folder 4)
  - Vaughn, Miles and Peg, 1930-1932 (Folder 5)
  - Velde, Harold, 1951-1954 (Folder 6)
  - Veth, Christl, 1936-1945 (Folder 7)
  - Vezey, V. Custis, 1918-1938 (Folder 8)
  - Viereck, George S., 1947-1950 (Folder 9)
  - Villard, Oswald G., 1943-1946 (Folder 10)
  - Vlachos-Wei, T. V., 1947-1948 (Folder 11)
  - Vlugt, Ebed van der, 1949 (Folder 12)
  - Von Wiegand, Karl H., 1945-1959 (Folder 13)
  - Votaw, Maurice, 1951-1953 (Folder 14)
  - Walck, Henry Z., 1951-1961 (Folder 15)
  - Waldman, Louis, 1940-1956 (Folder 16)
  - Waldrop, Frank, 1944-1955 (Folder 17)
  - Wallace, Dewitt, 1942-1952 (Folder 18)
  - Wallace, Henry, 1932-1953 (Folder 19)
  - Wallace, Mike, 1960 (Box 118, Folder 1)
  - Walpin, Michael, 1951-1960 (Folder 2)
  - Walsh, Cornelius, 1957-1961 (Folder 3)
  - Walsh, Christy, 1947-1952 (Folder 4)
  - Walsh, Monica Barry, 1950 (Folder 5)
  - Walsh, Neil, 1954-1962 (Folder 6)
  - Walters, Barbara, 1960-1961 (Folder 7)
  - Wampler, Cloud, 1947-1953 (Folder 8)
  - Wang, Cheng-t'ing
    - 1920-1923 (Folder 9)
    - 1924-1938 (Folder 10)
  - Wanger, Walter, 1948-1959 (Folder 11)
  - Ward, Clifford, 1947-1949 (Folder 12)
  - Ward, Stuart R., 1953-1955 (Folder 13)
  - Waring, Fred, 1951 (Folder 14)
  - Waring, Thomas, 1954-1962 (Folder 15)
  - The Washington Post, 1954-1960. Includes correspondence with Philip L. Graham and James R. Wiggins (Box 119, Folder 1)
  - Waterbury Republican, 1947-1956 (Folder 2)
  - Watkins, Arthur V., 1952 (Folder 3)
  - Watkins, Charles Mason, 1959-1960 (Folder 4)
  - Wazeter, Francis, 1951-1961 (Folder 5)
  - Wayne, John, 1961 (Folder 6)
  - Weaver, Bertrand, 1942-1944 (Folder 7)
  - Webb, William J., 1950 (Folder 8)
  - Wedemeyer, Albert C., 1948-1960 (Folder 9)
  - Wegman, Edward, 1941 (Folder 10)
  - Wehle, Louis B., 1950 (Folder 11)
  - Weigold, Arthur G., 1955-1959 (Folder 12)
  - Weinberg, Harold M., 1938-1943 (Folder 13)
  - Weir, Ernest T., Mr. and Mrs.
    - 1937-1942 (Folder 14)
    - 1943-1945 (Folder 15)
    - 1946-1957 (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - Weir, Walter, 1950 (Folder 2)